General
Marist Archives and Special Collections
General
2.1.9.1.2
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1611
- General, 2.1.9.1.2
  - Olive Enequist Elger and Lowell Thomas [color photographs], 1977; 9 (Box 1611)
    - With Olive Enequist Elger Dec. 1977 (I think), At a dinner for Excelsior Foundation - Girl's school Denver, Colorado. I'm just about a year late in sending this to you, 1
    - Verso: With Olive Enequist Elger Dec. 1977 (I think), At a dinner for Excelsior Foundation - Girl's school Denver, Colorado. I'm just about a year late in sending this to you, 1-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and Olive Enequist Elger Dec 1977, Dinner for Excelsior Girl's School Denver, Colorado, 2
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and Olive Enequist Elger Dec 1977, Dinner for Excelsior Girl's School Denver, Colorado, 2-verso
  - Pauline and David Enequist [color photograph], 1979; 10 (Box 1611)
    - [Man and woman standing outside of building], 1
  - Winifield Eng, Jr., 1955; 11 (Box 1611)
    - You may have guessed that I am an American-Chinese - Therefore my interests in the subject stems from a personal interest in the traditions which prevail on my heritage - I'm proud of my twins - Pauline and Pamela and a beautiful Chinese wife, 1
    - Verso: You may have guessed that I am an American-Chinese - Therefore my interests in the subject stems from a personal interest in the traditions which prevail on my heritage - I'm proud of my twins - Pauline and Pamela and a beautiful Chinese wife
  - Annie Irving, 1939; 12 (Box 1611)
    - Mrs. Annie Irving New Glasgow N.J., 1
    - Verso: Mrs. Annie Irving New Glasgow N.J., 1-verso
  - Mr. and Mrs. Herbert Janes [color photograph], 1980; 13 (Box 1611)
    - Nov. 79; Ginny and "Hons" Janes, 1
    - Verso: Nov. 79; Ginny and "Hons" Janes, 1-verso
  - Linea H. Jenkins [color photograph], 1973; 14 (Box 1611)
    - Since I don't like writing to a faceless name, this is a picture of me, 1
    - Verso: Since I don't like writing to a faceless name, this is a picture of me, 1-verso
  - Bob Jennings [color photograph], 1975; 15 (Box 1611)
    - Bob Jennings TV Sales Inc.; RCA & GE Color-Hammond Organs; Jacuzzi Whirlpool Units; Brookfield Center, Conn., 1
    - Verso: Bob Jennings TV Sales Inc.; RCA & GE Color-Hammond Organs; Jacuzzi Whirlpool Units; Brookfield Center, Conn., 1-verso
  - Hattie Jessup [color photograph], 1980; 16 (Box 1611)
    - Compliments of "Juneau Hattie"& ("formerly"&); "Red "Dog"& Saloon"&; Juneau, Alaska, (1954); Age 88, 1
    - Verso: Compliments of "Juneau Hattie"& ("formerly"&); "Red "Dog"& Saloon"&; Juneau, Alaska, (1954); Age 88, 1-verso
  - Bob Johnson, 1969; 17 (Box 1611)
    - Yours Truly! Bob Johnson; Robert R. Johnson; Feb. 1969; 312 West Bute St; Norfolk, Va. 23510, 1
    - Verso: Yours Truly! Bob Johnson; Robert R. Johnson; Feb. 1969; 312 West Bute St; Norfolk, Va. 23510, 1-verso
  - W. H. Johnson, 1967; 18 (Box 1611)
    - [Portrait of man wearing glasses], 1
  - Nathalie and Ted Jones [color photograph], 1969; 19 (Box 1611)
    - Caption: Greetings& from our home to yours! Nathalie and Ted, 1
  - Josephine Kaas [includes photographs of Lowell Thomas], 1942; 20 (Box 1611)
    - [Lowell Thomas on a field], 1
    - Eugene Ouell; PO Box 522; Pawling N.Y., 2
    - Verso: Eugene Ouell; PO Box 522; Pawling N.Y., 2-verso
    - [?], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas on baseball field], 4
    - [Group of men playing instruments on field], 5
    - [People on baseball field], 6
    - [Three people by body of water], 7
    - [Group of boys at baseball field], 8
    - [Children at baseball field (LT, Jr. at left?], 9
    - Note: Chief Rising Sun at Lowell Thomas, 10
  - Edward T. Keenan, 1947; 21 (Box 1611)
    - [Man sitting in chair in front of bookshelves], 1
  - Paul E. Kelly [color photograph], 1967; 22 (Box 1611)
    - Caption: Season's Greetings Tucker, Jack E., Paul E. Jr., Diane, and Paul Kelly, 1
    - Verso: Season's Greetings; The Paul E. Kellys; 322 South State Road; Briarcliff Manor, NY 10510, 1-verso
  - J. Leslie Kincaid, 1972; 23 (Box 1611)
    - Verso: 1966, 1
    - Verso: 1966, 1-verso
  - Ralph Korpi, circa 1958; 24 (Box 1611)
    - Ralph Korpi, 1
    - Verso: Ralph Korpi, 1-verso
  - Charles J. Lovett, Jr., 1939; 25 (Box 1611)
    - [no description], 1
    - Note: The Season's Greetings for a good old-fashioned Merry Christmas and a mighty glad New Year; Charles J. Lovett, Jr., 2
  - Bruce Rinaldo, 1941; 26 (Box 1611)
    - To Lowell Thomas from whom I've derived so much of interest! Most Sincerely Bruce Rinaldo; Abstractor, Pennsylvania Historical Survey - Erie, Pa. 6/2/'41, 1
    - Verso: To Lowell Thomas from whom I've derived so much of interest! Most Sincerely Bruce Rinaldo; Abstractor, Pennsylvania Historical Survey - Erie, Pa. 6/2/'41, 1-verso
  - Doctor Paul A. Siple, 1941; 27 (Box 1611)
    - From more than 100 aerial photographs taken by Dr. Paul A. Siple, official cartographer of the U. S. Antarctic Service Expedition&, 1
    - Note: From more than 100 aerial photographs taken by Dr. Paul A. Siple, official cartographer of the U. S. Antarctic Service Expedition to the South Pole Country, Artist Beverly Towles executed this sketch of "Colonel Albanus Phillips Mountains"&, 200 miles north-east of Little America, on the Antarctic Continent. The newly charted chain is 80 miles long, 30 miles wide and over 6,000 feet high, 2
  - Mother Rankin and Ruffus Stoddard, 1940; 28 (Box 1611)
    - Mother Rankin; Son Ruffus Stoddard, 1
    - Verso: Mother Rankin; Son Ruffus Stoddard, 1-verso
  - Thistle Down Jockey Club, 1939; 29 (Box 1611)
    - [Horse race], 1
    - [Horse race], 2
    - Note: Envelope than contained photographs, 3
  - George Williams, 1939; 30 (Box 1611)
    - [View of ocean and palm leaves], 1
    - [Portrait of man], 2
    - Note: George Williams; Director "Radio Newspaper"&; Commercial Agent; HP5G and HOA, 3
  - Olive C. Wilson, circa 1949; 31 (Box 1611)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter from Olive C. Wilson to Lowell Thomas, Page 1], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter from Olive C. Wilson to Lowell Thomas, Page 2], 2
    - [LT, Sr. and LT, Jr. with another man], 3
    - [Two men standing together], 4
    - [LT, Sr. and LT, Jr. with another man], 5
    - [LT, Sr. and LT, Jr. with another man], 6
    - [Close-up picture of a man], 7
    - [Close-up picture of a man], 8
    - [LT, Sr. standing with another man], 9
    - [LT, Sr. standing by car], 10
  - Mr. and Mrs. Colin Wyatt, 1941; 32 (Box 1611)
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1] Introducing Mr. and Mrs. Colin Wyatt, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2] Mr. Colin Wyatt is an Englishman educated in Switzerland and Cambridge Universities&, 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3] During this period he served on the Council of the Ski Club of Great Britain and was also a Member of various other Committees&, 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4] In the winter of 1938 Mr. Wyatt lead an expedition across Arctic Lapland on skis from Sweden across Finland to North Cape&, 4
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 5] Mrs. Wyatt is also at home in the snow, is a keen skier and holds the Australian Bronze Medal&, 5
    - [Photographs removed from document], 6
    - Verso: [signed] Colin W. Wyatt, 6-verso
    - [Photographs removed from document], 7
    - Verso: [signed] Colin W. Wyatt, 7-verso
    - [Photographs removed from document], 8
    - Verso: [signed] Colin W. Wyatt, 8-verso
    - [Photographs removed from document], 9
    - Cedar Lodge, Riverton, UT. Looking north, 10
    - Verso: Cedar Lodge, Riverton, UT. Looking north, 10-verso
    - Cedar Lodge, Riverton, UT. Looking south and showing one of the meadows and part of the woodland. Much higher than appears. E. H. Prouty, Agt., 11
    - Verso: Cedar Lodge, Riverton, UT. Looking south and showing one of the meadows and part of the woodland. Much higher than appears. E. H. Prouty, Agt., 11-verso